maisonette.com 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy - Maisonette Children's Shop Privacy Policy - Maisonette

_Last Revised: March 6, 2017_

MAISONETTE (“Company”, “we”, “us” or “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website located at maisonette.com (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how we may collect, use, and share information gathered from you as you visit the Site, and is a binding agreement between you and the Company. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, you must immediately cease your use of the Site. We may update this Policy from time to time, and your use of the Site constitutes your express acceptance to the terms of the then-posted version of this Policy.

### Information Collection

“Personal Information” means any information that can be used to identify you individually. We collect Personal Information you voluntarily provide us. including, without limitation, your name; your billing and shipping address(es); your email address; your phone number; and your credit card information. You may refuse to provide Personal Information, but some parts of the Site may not be fully available or functional without submitting such information. Even if you do not register with us, when you interact with our Site, we may collect the following: your IP address, device type, operating system, browser, and other Site usage details such as page views, clicks, and duration of page visits. 

In addition to Personal Information, our servers automatically collect certain anonymous, aggregate and/or technical information that does not identify you personally (“Anonymous Data”). 

### Cookies

The Site may also include tracking technologies such as “cookies” – small data file identifiers that are transferred to your computer or mobile device to recognize your browser or mobile device and transfer information about you and your use of our Site. Cookies automatically help us provide a tailored experience when you visit the Site. You may disable cookies in your browser settings, but some parts of the Site may not be fully available or functional without cookies.

### Use of Information

We use your Personal Information for the purpose for which you submitted it (for example, to order and receive products from our Site). We may also use your information to communicate with you about your orders and account and provide you with customer support when needed. This may require us to provide your information to third parties including our partner boutiques from whom you are purchasing your product and our delivery partners. Other purposes for which we use Personal Information are marketing purposes, Site administration and optimization, and fraud detection and prevention. We may also use Personal Information to protect the security of the Site and its systems, to investigate and respond to any suspected breaches of the Site or its systems, and to cooperate as we deem reasonable with legal requests and proceedings. 

We may use Anonymous Data for any purpose we deem appropriate, including without limitation to maintain and improve the Site and our current and future products and services.

### Sharing of Information

We may share Personal Information with our affiliates. We may also share Personal Information with third parties: (i) in connection with a court order, subpoena, government investigation, or when otherwise required by law; (ii) in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, or similar event; or (iii) in connection with their services regarding the operation, maintenance, or improvement of the Site on our behalf. We will not sell or share any Personal Information to third parties except as set forth in this Policy. We may share Anonymous Data to third parties for any purpose we deem appropriate. 

### Options

If at any time you wish to opt-out of future newsletters or other promotional emails, you may click the “unsubscribe” link in the email or otherwise contact us at [info@maisonette.com](mailto:info@maisonette.com). It may take up to 10 business days before you stop receiving promotional emails. This opt-out does not apply to operational communications, for example, order confirmation emails.

### Information about Children

This Site is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from children under 13 on the Site. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register an account or send any information about yourself to us. If we discover that we have collected Personal Information from children under 13, we will take commercially reasonable measures to promptly delete such information from our systems. If you are younger than age 18, you may use the Site only with the permission and involvement of your parent or guardian. If a parent or guardian becomes aware of his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, please contact us at [info@maisonette.com](mailto:info@maisonette.com). 

### Security

We maintain technical, administrative, physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of Personal Information provided to us. We take reasonable steps to protect Personal Information, including: using Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) to encrypt your credit card number, name and address; requiring you to establish a password to access your account on the Site; not keeping details of your credit card that would enable any third party to transact using that credit card (such as your CCV number); and regularly monitoring our servers and IT systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks. Unfortunately, despite these efforts, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of Personal Information transmitted to or through our Site, and any such transmission is at your own risk. 

### Third Party Sites

The Site contains links to third party websites. We cannot control, and take no responsibility for, the content or privacy practices of such third-party websites. Please carefully review the privacy policy and any other applicable terms for such third-party websites.

### Contact

If you have any further questions concerning this Policy, or would like to correct, update, or delete such information, please contact [info@maisonette.com](mailto:info@maisonette.com).

### Policy Updates

This Policy was last updated on March 6, 2017. Any changes we may make to this Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back regularly to keep informed of updates or changes to this Privacy Policy.
